

Jui-Hsin, Wong eric032807@gmail.com +886987666405

Objective

I am 24 years old and graduated from the Department of Information and Computer Education of National Taiwan Normal University. I have been using computers since 14 years old, so I am very familiar with computers and have experience in remote work. I usually use the Internet to follow news and memes from Taiwan and the world.

Education

National Taiwan Normal University 2020-2022 M.S.Ed. Information and Computer Education

Tamkang University 2016-2020

B.E. Educational Techlolgy

Work Experience

Research Assistant	2020-present
Distance Education Development center part-time worker	2018 - 2020

Requirements

- 1. I have a smartphone (ios 15.4.1) and a laptop.
- 2. Live in Taiwan for 24 years.
- 3. I use a lot of social media including Facebook, PTT, Youtube, Instagram